Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun attacked the Forest of Witches for a magic stone.
During the chaos, the Diamond Kingdom's army arrived to steal a secret spell from the Queen of Witches.
Millions lasers!
I think I'll start by killing this noisy little witch.
Coming off!
Everything that you said, well I guess it finally hit home.
That's when Mars, member of the Diamond Army and Fonzel's former student, decided to rethink his loyalties.
Why would you help us?
Ladros is right. The two of us are traitors. I mean, losing your memories.
Not to worry, sir. I've decided I'm on your side.
Bounce it over here!
Don't see why, but sure!
Thanks to Asta's anti-magic, our friends were finally able to defeat Ladros.
But Fon of the Midnight Sun, despite being hit with Noelle's water magic, proved more difficult to subdue.
FONNA!
It's me, remember? Please tell me you still recognize me!
I know that girl. I taught her.
Confused by her memory loss, Fon of prepared to self-destruct.
Everything must be destroyed!
But as Mars and Asta fought desperately to stop her...
Fon, let's go and explore together!
We said we would, so, let's go.
The memories of her past were restored.
Imagine seule!
The memories of her past were squares.
We knew it was one moment for her night.
cyclical mother, Fon.
The memories of her past were 무슨 cosy through the night.
hores who Mer bezpal, Stephen find her a pretty similar demille.
What?
We seek a셨어요 about your situation...
I'll see you next time.
And it's because of you.
The battlefield is a place of power.
On it, there is no room for the weak.
That's why I was born.
To destroy those like you.
You're in my way.
Begone!
Only those who are strong will survive.
The weak deserve death.
You're a pathetic, helpless little child.
You never stood a chance of defeating me!
No, that was all you, Mars.
You're tough.
I knew you'd be able to save your friend.
Hold on.
Are the two of you already acquainted?
Sort of.
Oh, wow.
So you made a friend in the outside world.
That's wonderful to hear.
Well, we're not really...
Yep, that's right.
We're buddies.
Even though we did fight that one time.
That hurts.
Ow, my hand!
I'm glad you've relaxed a little, too.
So what the heck happened to make you go crazy?
This way you always fly back to the seat of your pants.
You could have been killed!
How did you survive this land doing reckless stuff like that?
Put the blues on already!
I have to tell you, Mars, you really are an outstanding pupil.
Thank you for everything, Master.
Master Fonzo.
Your powers are meant for protecting people, and nothing else.
Don't ever forget that, okay?
Right!
I'm so happy both of you were alive.
You barely remember anything?
Right.
I do recall something from after training.
Has the girl really come back to life?
Is this because of that phoenix magic?
Or perhaps...
I see.
Then we should entrust a magic stone to Fauna as well.
How disappointing.
Her magic power should be heightened, but it's practically depleted.
Down to the last dying embers.
Throw her away.
She is of no further interest to me.
How tragic.
To think you were my friend.
I suppose this world never changes.
If humans are so determined to harm each other,
then we'll just help them along.
However, you're going to need your body, so...
Let's keep you alive.
Everything after that is a blank.
It was like somebody was possessing me,
and they controlled everything that I did.
All I remember is feeling that person's intense hatred.
What about your third eye in those pointy ears?
I'm sorry, but I really don't know.
All of that time?
How could I have been so oblivious?
It's all right.
There's nothing that you need to feel guilty about.
It brought us back together, didn't it?
True.
And I'm not letting you go.
Oh my...
You're right.
We'd better stick together.
Uh, yeah.
Ooh, things are heating up over there.
And look how tense and awkward the poor guy is.
It's so adorable.
A happy reunion of two childhood friends
torn apart by tragedy.
What a wonderful thing to witness!
Whoa, those are some serious waterworks.
I can't tell if you're happy or sad.
I'm jealous, sad, and angry.
I'll put together.
What do you mean?
Did you never have any childhood buddies?
Oh, let's be honest, Asta.
I never had one as cute as she is,
and we both know him!
Even I have friends from when I was little.
The whole bunch of them.
If you're saying that to make me jealous,
it's not working!
Not sure how I deserve that!
You should respect royalty.
I don't get it.
Why did the Eye of the Midnight Sun
come to the Forest of Witches to start with?
What's wrong?
I still feel their thoughts.
Whoever was controlling my mind earlier
was saying that they wanted to take back
the magic stone.
Huh?
Magic stone?
Does that mean one of them is in the forest?
Then we have to hurry back to where the Queen is!
Hold on.
First things first,
let's make sure everyone's safe.
Domina, Mariela, and all those witches.
What kind of key is this?
What the?
That power should be gone!
Everyone, run away!
You're right!
That was an awful lot of magic you fed me.
It took a few good minutes to absorb all of it.
Thanks for the meal!
For a second there,
I was sure I was a goner!
It can't be.
You were out of power.
No, I just fired it all off
and then pulled it back in.
You're pretty good at magic detection, Teach,
but you rely on that way too much.
And while we're on the subject,
I have a question.
Why are all you softies so quick
to throw your own lives away
to save somebody else's?
No.
I'll kill you.
That's the smartest thing
you've said all day.
Oh, wonderful.
Now this little reject's
trying to interfere.
Step aside, Shorty.
This doesn't concern you.
Of course it does.
I can't let you hurt him.
He's my friend.
Why are all you softies so quick
to throw your own lives away
to save somebody else's?
No.
I'll kill you.
That's the smartest thing
you've said all day.
Ah!
Oh, wonderful.
Now this little reject's
trying to interfere.
Step aside, Shorty.
This doesn't concern you.
Of course it does.
I can't let you hurt him.
He's my friend.
Basta.
Oh, no.
Here, I'll heal you.
It failed?
Is there something wrong with me?
Am I out of magic power?
Ha ha ha ha!
You just stay there.
Leave this jerk to me!
Whoa!
Wait a second, kid.
I think I recognize you.
You're that magicless knight
who fights using anti-magic,
aren't you?
Trust me.
I know your pain.
I was born without
a magic attribute.
Isn't that something?
When I was growing up,
all the other kids
used to make fun of me
and say that I was
bland and boring.
But hey,
at least I had magic, right?
Unlike you.
Shut your mouth
or I'll shut it for you!
I feel sorry for you.
Then give me your magic!
You know, I certainly would if I could.
Ugh, fine.
Can you reach it?
You are the funniest little fella, you know that?
I think the two of us can make a pretty stellar team.
Wanna join forces? I can make you my right-hand man.
I'll put in a good word for you with the Diamond Kingdom Army
and you and I can climb through the ranks together.
What do you say?
We've got what it takes to beat everyone who ever looks down their noses at us!
Joke's on him.
All I'm planning to do is soak up those anti-magic powers for myself.
Forget it.
Huh?
No deal!
I'm gonna be the Clover Kingdom's Wizard King!
Wizard King, huh?
That's cute.
Maybe you're not a good sidekick.
You're two deaths.
A million lasers!
Sweet little no-match at night!
I know a few things about how you operate!
For example, now that your spatial mage is out of commission,
you'll be helpless against long-distance attacks!
You're a sitting duck!
And don't bother bouncing anything back at me!
Cause I can just recycle it!
You can't win!
You might as well give up now!
You may know some things about me, but if you think you can hurt my friends and get away with it, then you don't know me at all!
Friends, huh?
There's no such thing as friends.
This world has two types of people.
Those who use, and those who get used.
I made it where I am by using the ones you'd call my friends.
That includes our poor defeated Marzy boy and his little girlfriend.
I plan to use those two to my benefit as well.
They can live out the rest of their pitiful lives as test subjects in the Diamond Army's magic lab!
What's wrong?
Still think I won't get away with it?
You're about to become my stepping stone too!
Oh!
This is bad.
No!
My magic power is dwindling fast!
And it doesn't feel so great either!
It won't budge!
Are you kidding me?!
Is this really the way I'm gonna go out?!
After stockpiling that much magic, I dropped my guard for a second and all this smoke and that's it?!
And I just made Shining General 2!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
This can't be happening!
It's not fair!
All he had to do was chuck that big stupid heavy sword up there one time and he'd knock me right out of the sky!
Man, talking about perfect aim!
And now look what a sorry state I'm in!
Damn it all!
Time for a last ditch effort!
I can't let myself be defeated by a fluke of an attack like this!
In fact, I won't!
Stay back!
Don't hurt me!
I didn't make it this far all on my own either.
I was taught how to fight, how to use my strength!
My friends and I honed our skills together by always having each other's backs!
You wanna know how I've been able to respond to his attacks?
It's cause I've been picking up on something that the people back in my country called Ki.
Ki?
There's a saying where I'm from.
Whatever happens, a warrior never goes back on his word.
You did say you were gonna be the wizard king, right?
This is where you gotta push past your limits.
If you don't, then your path ends here.
Yes, sir!
Water creation magic!
Sea Dragon's Cradle!
What are you three doing?
Good thing I'm here!
Great timing!
Everything is riding...
On this single shot!
Nothing but a failure!
That's not me anymore!
Water creation magic!
Sea Dragon's War!
No way!
Let us give you a hand with that new move!
Water creation magic!
Sea Dragon's War!
No way!
Let us give you a hand with that new move.
Here we go!
Your special move is gonna be incredible!
It's too late!
You're not killing anybody, you hear me?!
No thrust!
We won!
Alright!
My special move totally kicked our butt!
You think friends only exist so you can use them?
Well, that's not how we do things.
Real friends are always helping each other get better!
Yeah, I was wrong, and I'm sorry!
I promise I'll never hurt anyone again!
Just help me! I'm begging you!
Come on!
Just take the thorn out, Asta!
Hurry, I can't do it by myself!
Yeah, right!
I know how strong you are!
No way am I gonna fall for that!
If I do it and you fight back, I'm dead meat!
Heck, if I had missed, I'd be dead right now!
Just how stupid do you think I am, pal?!
Wait, please don't kill me!
I won't last much longer this way!
It wasn't a fatal stab!
You're gonna be okay!
Ah, damn it!
I thought I could appeal to his emotions, but he's not as stupid as I expected!
This kid's obviously learned a thing or two from all the tough battles he's fought!
Looks like the best option is to hit you real hard so you pass out!
This is gonna hurt!
Ah!
Please, no!
I have a little magic left!
If I can hit this and dodge him, I'll be in the clear!
Maybe I could force it out with reinforcement magic!
I've got enough to muster two magical bullets!
Leave her alone!
Hi there!
It's Fauna, right?
Let me go!
I don't know how you got your pretty little hands on such a ridiculous amount of power,
but I'm gonna need you to cast that super strong spell now!
Huh?
Super strong spell?
W-what do you mean?
Don't play dumb with me!
Hurry up and get to it!
Or he dies!
Oh no!
It'll only take one more to kill him!
I won't let you!
There you go!
Now it's time to pull out all the stops for the grand finale!
Yeah!
DUDE!
What a outrageous power!
My old bodies bursting at the same!
By all bodies bursting at the same!
Uh!
Oh, that hits the spot.
No doubt about it, that was the most delicious magic power I've ever had the pleasure of consuming.
What is this? Spirits aren't even capable of generating that much.
The fact that he can hold it at all is downright inhuman.
What the hell if you're done?
That's it!
Sorry, it's my turn.
I can track his key, but he's way too fast to dodge.
With a spell like this, I'm unstoppable.
I can't wait to put all the other shiny generals to shame.
And more than that, the entire kingdom will be mine for the taking.
I'll make the world pay dearly for looking down on me.
But before I do, guess I should finish what I started, huh?
You won't sneak up on me again!
I'm going to hit you with a barrage of long-distance attacks!
Soon your body will be torn to smithereens!
Asta, no!
My, how imperfect.
Since he's able to wield that sword, I had assumed he must be a member of that bloodline.
Why don't we show them what you really are?
Tell me tough guy, how many more of these magic blasts do you think you could suffer before you die?
Hmm?
I can't wait for it.
I can't wait for it!
Maybe?
Because I'm going to die since the last time this last time!
We'll be right back.
Clover Clips!
How's it taste?
Oh, that hits the spot.
No doubt about it, that was the most delicious magic power I've ever had the pleasure of consuming.
Here!
Mmm, that tastes sophisticated.
Leave it to royalty.
Here.
Mmm, and your magic's got a bit of a mature flavor to it.
Take this.
Oh wow, that one tastes so familiar, it just gave me a rush of nostalgia.
Really?
Yeah!
It kinda tastes like a bunch of prunes!
First you said I look old and now you're telling me my magic tastes old too?
Yup, that's the gist of it teach!
What did the queen do to you, Asta?
Your grimoire's got an eerie glow!
And why do you look like some kind of evil demon?
Black Clover page 63.
Not in the slightest.
A shooting star black as the night sky.
Purple世界 and Blue Ocean.
Black Clover Lake.
Beauty
Eyes on Earth.
liebe
ng
angen